ASAOLU AYODEJI MICHAEL

Address: 26, Fagbamila Street, Agodi Gate

Phone: 08067175357

Facebook: Asaolu Ayodeji Michael

Gmail: asaolu111@gmail.com

Linkedin:Linkedin.com/in/ayodeji-asaolu-62a0b2208

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

A very good experience in marketing and customer relations with over 6 years as a marketing executive, 3 years as digital marketer and motion graphics designer. An avid communicator with demonstrated capacity of driving sales skills and building strong relationship with a team and customers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Date

2021-06 to 2021-11 **CMG(Cedarstrip mercantile group,contract)**

Cedarstrip investment company, Lagos state

- Recording of weekly activities and Training users
- Bringing users to Payspot BIZ(APK)

2020-03 to 2021-03

Secretary (NYSC)

African high school, Ikere Ekiti

- Dissemination of information to staff, students and parents.
- Maintain variety of computerized and manual record
- Assist other personnel for the purpose of supporting them in the completion of their work activities

2013-06 to 2020

Sales Representative

Rapido Venture- Owerri, Imo state

• Enhance sales operations through development of new sales strategies, cold calling techniques and customer follow- up

- Answering customer's questions and escalating complex issues to the relevant department as needed
- Maintaining an accurate record of all sales, scheduled customer appointment and customer complaints.
- Informing product developer of possible product improvement and changes to ensure that company products meant current market needs.
- Attend to customers need and meet

2011-10 To 2013 -05

Supervisor

Marig concept- Akure, Ondo State

- Meet with customers to discuss services needs and develop effective and practical solutions
- Planning and management of recourses to consistently met production, quality and cost goals
- Manage operations, including ordering materials and supplies.

COMPUTER_SKILLS

- Proficiency in Microsoft suite (words, Excel, PowerPoint)
- ♣ Digital Marketing
- ☆ Motion Graphics Designer
- ♣ Graphics Design
- **♦** Web development

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- **♣** Documentation and Control
- **†** Communication Skills
- **†** Leadership Skills
- **†** Marketing Research
- **†** Performance improvement
- **♦** Management Skills
- **♦** Strategic planning and tactical execution

EDUCATION:

2017-2019	HND in Marketing	Rufus Giwa Polytechnic
2014-2016	ND in Marketing	Rufus Giwa Polytechnic

2002-2008	Secondary School certificate	Omoluorogbo Grammar School		
1998-2002	Primary School Certificate	Saint James Primary School		
CERTIFICATION				
 Content writing at Alison school 		2019		
Google digital skills for Africa		2021		
ACHIEVEMENTS				

• Developed relationship with 67 new clients and typically exceeded sales goals by 20% **Awards:**

REFERENCES

Mr. Oriade Isijola Pastor Adeniji Adesida

CEO of Marig Integrated Farm Akure Civil Servant

Phone Number: 08060446368 Phone 08034277176

Emaill: easyj70@yahoo.com